>> Hi there. Welcome to yet another Python series in
• 嗨，您。欢迎光临 另一个 Python 系列
case you or sick of us already we're back for more.
你或我们生病的情况下 我们已经回来了更多。
This time we're going to focus in on some tools for data science.
这一次，我们将专注于 在数据科学的一些工具上。
Now, before we get into it,
现在，在我们进入它之前，
there's really three main questions
真的有三个主要问题
that we want to be able to answer.
我们希望能够回答。
Who are we, who are you
我们是谁，你是谁
and what is it that we're going to be doing here?
是什么，我们 会在这里做什么？
So let's start off with, well, who are we?
让我们开始 我们和谁一起？
>> So my name is Susan Ibach and I am
所以我的名字是苏珊·伊巴赫，我是
definitely a data geek also known as hockeygeekgirl online,
绝对是一个数据极客也 被称为曲棍球女孩在线，
and one of the things that I loved to do when I'm
和事情之一， 我喜欢做，当我
not sitting in front of a terminal coding,
不坐在前面 终端编码，
I'm probably either maybe running
我可能在跑步
a marathon or maybe listening some good thrash fan.
马拉松，也许听 一些好鞭打风扇。
>> As for me, I'm Christopher Harrison.
至于我，我 克里斯托弗·哈里森
I've been a geek for about as long as I can remember.
我一直是个怪人 只要我能记得
I'm now a Program Manager at or with
我现在是一个项目经理在或
academic ecosystems inside of Microsoft,
学术生态系统 微软内部，
I've a propensity to tell dad jokes,
我有一种倾向告诉爸爸笑话
as well as saying the word
以及说这个词
"Propensity" I'm a husband, I'm a marathoner,
"倾向"我是一个 丈夫 我是马拉松运动员
and I'm a father of a four-legged child,
我是父亲 一个四条腿的孩子
also known as a dog.
也被称为狗。
So let's talk a little bit then about like expectations,
所以，让我们谈谈一点点 然后就像期望一样
prerequisites, if you will, basically,
先决条件，如果 基本上你会
who are you and why is
你是谁，为什么是
it that you might be interested in something like this?
它可能有兴趣 像这样？
So the assumption that we're making is that you've done
因此，假设我们 让你做的
a little bit of Python and you're looking to
一点点的Python 你正在寻找
just get in and start to explore data science that
只是进入并开始 探索数据科学，
maybe there's a quick start that you'll want to check
也许有一个快速的开始 你会想检查
out and you're just trying to figure out like,
出来，你只是试图 想搞清楚
what are these different things that I'm being told to
这些有什么不同 事情，我被告知
just follow along with and just run some code.
只是跟着 并运行一些代码。
Hopefully, we'll explain some of what's going on inside of there.
希望我们能解释一些 里面发生了什么
>> Yeah, because a lot of times,
是的，因为很多时候
a lot of people get into Python because I have
很多人进入 Python 因为我有
an interest in exploring that world of data science,
有兴趣探索 数据科学的世界，
but opening up that first data science tutorial,
但打开，第一 数据科学教程，
you've got all the data science concepts and at the same time
你拥有所有的数据科学 概念，同时
all kinds of new Python libraries
各种新的 Python 库
and debates that you might not be familiar with.
和辩论，你可能会 不熟悉。
So what we're hoping here is introduce you to some of
所以，我们希望在这里 是介绍你到一些
those Python tools and some of
那些Python工具和一些
those libraries so that maybe
那些图书馆，所以也许
when you do that data science tutorial,
当您执行该数据时 科学教程，
you can focus more on just new data science concepts.
你可以更专注于只是 新的数据科学概念。
>> Yeah, so that's really what it
是的，所以这就是它
is that we're going to be doing here, is introducing those,
是，我们要做 在这里，介绍那些，
those libraries, walk you
那些图书馆，走你
through some common tools and techniques,
通过一些常见的 工具和技术，
and navigate through some common scenarios.
并导航通过 一些常见的方案。
The way that we're going to be doing it is by walking
我们要的方式 做它是通过步行
through really some basic scenarios,
通过一些基本方案，
and you'll notice that there'll be a little bit of
你会注意到 会有一点点
a common thread throughout a lot of these modules,
贯穿始终的公用线程 很多这些模块
where a lot of these modules,
其中很多这些模块，
a lot of these concepts will build on the ones prior.
很多这些概念将 建立在之前的。
That being said, there still all designed to be snackable,
话虽如此，仍然有 所有设计是可零食的，
all just like really short.
都像真的很短。
So you can jump in,
所以你可以跳进去
take a look at the particular tools concepts that you need,
看看特定的 工具概念，你需要，
and then jump back out from there.
然后从那里跳回来
>> Yeah, but you'll find it easiest to learn
是的，但你会发现 最容易学习
these particular series if you do watch them sequentially.
这些特定的系列，如果你 按顺序观察它们。
You can still skip
您仍然可以跳过
the PowerPoint presentation and jump
PowerPoint 演示文稿和跳转
straight to demos if you're one of those people who are just,
直接演示，如果你是一个 那些只是人
"Just show me the code in
"只要给我看代码
action" You can still absolutely do that,
行动"你仍然可以 绝对这样做，
just follow the code modules,
只需遵循代码模块，
but you will probably find easier to follow
但你可能会 发现更容易跟随
the concepts if you do the modules in order.
概念，如果你这样做 模块顺序。
>> Yes, so let's head on into it.
• 是的，让我们一起进入它。
>> Let's start coding.
• 让我们开始编码。